|     |     |
| --- | --- |
|     | [](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Main_Page "Visit the main page")<br><br>* [Talk](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:MyTalk "Discussion about edits from this IP address [n]")<br>* [Contributions](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:MyContributions "A list of edits made from this IP address [y]")<br>* [Create account](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Special:CreateAccount&returnto=Wikisimpsons%3APrivacy+policy "You are encouraged to create an account and log in; however, it is not mandatory")<br>* [Log in](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Special:UserLogin&returnto=Wikisimpsons%3APrivacy+policy "You are encouraged to log in; however, it is not mandatory [o]") |
| [](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Main_Page "Visit the main page")<br><br>Essential pages<br><br>* [Main Page](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Main_Page)<br>* [Episodes](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/List_of_episodes)<br>* [Characters](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Category:Characters)<br>* [Locations](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Category:Locations)<br>* [Comics](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Comics_Main_Page)<br>* [Tapped Out](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Tapped_Out_portal)<br>* [Ask a question](https://answers.simpsonswiki.com/ask)<br>* [Recent changes](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:RecentChanges "A list of recent changes in the wiki [r]")<br>* [Random page](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Random "Load a random page [x]")<br>* [Random image](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Random/File)<br>* [Help](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Help:Contents "The place to find out")<br><br>Community<br><br>* [Policies](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Policies_and_Guidelines)<br>* [Rollback users](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Rollback)<br>* [Administrators](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Administrators)<br>* [Requests for Rights](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Requests_for_Rights)<br>* [Style Guides](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Category:Style_Guides)<br>* [Discord](https://discord.gg/XfHxBDQ)<br>* [Other webpages](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Other_webpages)<br>* [Wiki discussion](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Wiki_discussion)<br>* [Who's online](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:WhosOnline)<br><br>Wiki Stats<br><br>* [46,607 articles](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Statistics)<br>* [54,148 uploads](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Statistics)<br>* [1,356,762 edits](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Statistics)<br>* [32,919 users](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Statistics)<br><br>Tools<br><br>* [What links here](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:WhatLinksHere/Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy "A list of all wiki pages that link here [j]")<br>* [Related changes](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:RecentChangesLinked/Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy "Recent changes in pages linked from this page [k]")<br>* [Special pages](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:SpecialPages "A list of all special pages [q]")<br>* [Printable version](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&printable=yes "Printable version of this page [p]")<br>* [Permanent link](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&oldid=868971 "Permanent link to this revision of the page")<br>* [Page information](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&action=info "More information about this page")<br><br>Wiki Network<br><br>* [Svenska Wikisimpsons](https://sv.simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Huvudsida)<br>* [Wikisimpsons Answers](https://answers.simpsonswiki.com/)<br>* [The Springfield Shopper](https://news.simpsonswiki.com/)<br>* [Simpsonspedia](http://simpsonspedia.net/index.php?title=Simpsonspedia)<br><br>Affiliates<br><br>* [The Simpsons Comics Site](http://tscs.xtreemhost.com/)<br>* [Springfield Punx](http://springfieldpunx.blogspot.com/)<br>* [Dead Homer Society](https://deadhomersociety.wordpress.com/)<br>* [The Infosphere](http://theinfosphere.org/)<br>* [NIWA](http://niwanetwork.org/)<br>* [Other affiliates](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Affiliates)<br><br>Social Media<br><br>[Follow @simpsonswiki](https://twitter.com/simpsonswiki) | * [Project page](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy "View the project page [a]")<br>* [Discussion](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons_talk:Privacy_policy "Discussion about the content page [t]")<br>* [Edit this page](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&action=edit "Edit this page [e]")<br>* [History](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&action=history "Past revisions of this page [h]")<br><br>* New article from the Springfield Shopper: Season 36 News: Another Sneak Peek and an introuction by the crew for “O C’mon All Ye Faithful” have been released!<br>* New article from the Springfield Shopper: Season 36 News: A new Sneak Peek for “Homer and Her Sisters” has been released!<br>* New article from the Springfield Shopper: Season 36 News: Promotional Images for “Homer and Her Sisters” have been released!<br>* New article from the Springfield Shopper: Season 36 News: A new Sneak Peek for “O C’mon All Ye Faithful” has been released!<br>* Wikisimpsons needs more Featured Article, Picture, Quote, Episode and Comprehensive article nominations!<br>* Wikisimpsons has a Discord server! Click here for your invite! Join to talk about the wiki, Simpsons and Tapped Out news, or just to talk to other users.<br>* Make an account! It's easy, free, and your work on the wiki can be attributed to you.<br><br>[](http://twitter.com/simpsonswiki "Twitter")[](http://www.facebook.com/wikisimpsons "Facebook")[](https://discord.gg/GyneDH6 "Discord")<br><br>Wikisimpsons:Privacy policy<br>===========================<br><br>Wikisimpsons - The Simpsons Wiki<br><br>[](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/File:Clancy_Wiggum.png "That's the law!")<br><br>Wikisimpsons takes the privacy of its users very seriously, and as part of our commitment to protecting your privacy, we provide the following information with complete transparency as to how information collected from our users is accessed, stored, and used.<br><br>Wikisimpsons collects information on its users for use in two isolated objectives: **operational** and **analytical**.<br><br>* **Operational information** we collect is used only to conduct wiki operations, and is very limited in scope. We use this information to identify users from one another, and if requested, to notify them by email of any changes to pages on their watchlist. Information collected for operational use is limited to a user's username, encrypted password hash, email address, and the IP addresses used while editing the site. Registered users of the site are only identified publicly by their username, and all other information collected is only viewable by authorized staff members. Logged out users are publicly identified by their IP address when editing pages and no other operational information is collected.<br>* **Analytical information** we collect is used to determine how and by whom content on our site is being viewed and used. This information includes but is not limited to screen resolution, operating system, web browser, pages viewed, referrers, search terms, visit duration, IP addresses, and overall geographic location. This information is only viewable by authorized wiki staff members, and is never sold or shared with third parties. This information is stored within our own servers and we do not rely on third party analytics hosting for this purpose.<br><br>Wikisimpsons displays advertisements provided by Google on both its desktop and mobile websites. By using this site, information may be collected by Google or its advertisers through their ads and used by Google as outlined by [their privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). Wikisimpsons is not responsible for the storage or usage of data collected by third party advertising partners.<br><br>Wikisimpsons uses cookies for the purposes of identifying and distinguishing users and guests. Cookies are used for both operational and analytical purposes. You may at any time choose to block cookies without detriment to your experience browsing our site.<br><br>All content posted to the wiki, with the exception of data collected for the purposes described above, is licensed under the CC-BY-SA Creative Commons license. By posting or uploading information to our site, you are agreeing to release that information under this license and may forfeit the ability to later revoke or modify the information.<br><br>If you decide to post personal information (age, name, address, etc.) on the wiki, you are doing so at your own risk. Wikisimpsons is not responsible for anything that occurs as a result of posting personal information and recommends that you not reveal a large amount of personal information. Wikisimpsons may not be held responsible for, or under any circumstances be associated with the opinions expressed by, the content of any editable pages, as these are community endeavors and their content sometimes make unexpected and inappropriate detours from their original intent.<br><br>The staff of Wikisimpsons pledges to moderate these pages to the best of its abilities and ensure inappropriate content and opinions are not displayed on the website, as our intentions are to be a web site suitable for people of all ages. In a similar fashion, we cannot be held responsible or directly associated with the advertisements shown at our site, as they are served through a third party network. We will, however, do everything in our power to limit these ads to those which are suitable for people of all ages and, in the event that Wikisimpsons is informed of inappropriate advertising, certainly bring such an issue up with the advertising companies that sponsor it.<br><br>At any time, you have the right to request a copy of all of the personal identifiable information we have on file for you. Depending on whether or not you are registered with the site, this information may or may not include both operational and analytical information. At any time, you may request that we delete all of the analytical information we have on file about you. Operational information is essential to the function of our site and cannot be deleted, however, you may request that we modify your account information in such a way that it can no longer be used to identify you in any conceivable way. If you request that this action be taken on your account, please be advised that it will not be reversible as we will no longer have any way to verify you as the owner of your former account. You also may be prohibited from creating an additional account, as per our sockpuppet policy. All requests for information or deletion should be submitted in writing to legal \[at\] Wikisimpsons.com.<br><br>If you have any questions regarding Wikisimpsons's privacy policies, please use the [administrators](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Administrators "Wikisimpsons:Administrators") page to get in touch with one of Wikisimpsons's many knowledgeable team members, who will be more than happy to answer them for you.<br><br>Your usage of this site constitutes agreement to these terms as outlined above. If you do not agree with these terms, you must immediately cease usage of this website. This privacy policy is effective as of **May 26th, 2018**.<br><br>Retrieved from "[https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy\_policy&oldid=868971](https://simpsonswiki.com/w/index.php?title=Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy&oldid=868971)"<br><br>[Categories](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Special:Categories "Special:Categories"):<br><br>* [Wikisimpsons](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Category:Wikisimpsons "Category:Wikisimpsons")<br>* [Wikisimpsons policies](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Category:Wikisimpsons_policies "Category:Wikisimpsons policies")<br><br>* Modified on September 17, 2019, at 13:31.<br><br>* [Privacy policy](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:Privacy_policy "Wikisimpsons:Privacy policy")<br>* [About Wikisimpsons](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:About "Wikisimpsons:About")<br>* [Disclaimers](https://simpsonswiki.com/wiki/Wikisimpsons:General_disclaimer "Wikisimpsons:General disclaimer")<br>* [Site Status](https://status.simpsonswiki.com/)<br><br>* [](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/)<br>* [](https://www.mediawiki.org/) |

© 2024 Wikisimpsons. All Rights Reserved.

The Simpsons® is a registered trademark of 20th Century Fox.

cached December 14th 7:37 pm by ( web )
